Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com
No living creature was hurt during
the production of this show.
I've been waiting for this.
Don't hold yourself back, Bala Hatun.
It was a good move.
You took it well.
You are going to kill me, huh?
Didn't you tell me to not
hold myself back, Osman Bey?
Come on. Make your move.
Why would someone with
eyes like this...
...need a sword to kill.
These eyes aren't a weapon,
they are a shield, Osman Bey.
They protect me from the tyranny
of your eyes.
It's Aksu Hatun. I met her at
food house.
She is kind, talented and she
helped me a lot.
Thank you, Aksu sister!
Your sherbet is as good
as your name.
Her attitude is also good,
as her face.
Mashallah. Mashallah.
-Who is your husband? Do we know him?
-I don't have a husband yet, Osman Bey.
If not, then, it's your responsibility,
Bala.
Find a good husband for Aksu sister.
-Salam Alaikum, Osman Bey.
-Alaikum Salam, Abdurrahman Ghazi.
Sheikh Edebali sent news.
He is coming.
Thank Allah.
Osman Bey.
Targun Hatun is the new leader
of Cumans.
Our child Göktuğ is her right hand.
Mashallah.
I knew he would do it. He is a valiant.
He had been through many troubles for me.
Thank Allah.
So, you and Göktuğ will
take revenge from Osman?
He will pay with his life.
You falsely changed your religion.
Aren't you afraid of committing a sin?
I'll burn in hell for you, Osman Bey.
You'll die in hell for me, huh?
But I live in heaven.
I live with an angel...
...who imprisoned me in her eyes.
-I wish I saved some of that poison...
...and didn't run with a cure.
Because of what you have done to
me and my wife, you are banished!
And about you, Göktuğ,
you failed me.
You couldn't guard my enemy!
You are banished!
Because of a single mistake I've done,
you are forgetting what my brother and I did.
That's what I would expect from a man...
...who banishes the woman who
will burn in hell for him.
Do you think that you can beat Osman?
-Without Rome, you are nothing.
-Göktuğ!
If you want to take revenge,
you have to survive.
So, you need our support.
Our soldiers.
Our gold.
That's what you are after.
That's how you buy victory.
You'll give gold. I'll give soldiers.
Soldiers, huh?
Only soldiers?
I promise you soldier and support.
You should be giving me more than
soldiers.
We'll give you Osman's head.
You convinced me.
If you are so confident...
...let's see if you will convince Nikola.
-Targun, come with me.
We are going to Nikola.
-Göktuğ, you stay here.
-Göktuğ.
Stay with my man. If something happens
to me, you know what to do.
Targun Hatun's men want gold for loyalty.
Nikol wants men to fight with us.
For this reason, sooner or later,
they'll come together.
But I'm already ready.
What do you want to do, Osman Bey?
I will outplay you on their plot
with Targun Hatun.
Thank Allah.
Brother, talk to the lord of Koyunhisar,
Yorgo.
But tell me that I want to see
him in secret.
-What's on your mind, Osman Bey?
-He dreamed of being the lord of İnegöl.
But now he is getting his orders
from Nikola.
This is hurting his ego.
We'll give him the opportunity.
We'll take advantage of that.
Nikola will be enemies with all lords.
-All right, Osman Bey. All right.
-Nikola wants us to have more enemies.
He worked with the Mongols against us.
He wanted to sway Yavlak Arslan.
Now the Cumans. We don't know
who is next.
We'll prevent that.
I can't wait to take revenge
for my son.
But you are right, Osman Bey.
We should do what he does.
Give him more enemies.
Trade should go on.
Trade routes should always be open.
Süleyman and Melik Beys caravans
should be protected.
As soon as they enter our lands,
they are our responsibility.
With the gold we get from them,
we'll help the poor.
We'll support tribes that want to
run away from the Mongols.
May Allah help you, Osman Bey.
Amin, amin, Bamsı Bey.
Amin.
I'll lose my head if we fail.
Not only me, Hazal Hatun too.
Dündar Bey, if you do everything
I say...
...no one will even bleed.
Only Osman's reputation.
When he loses his fur,
you will ascend.
Think of everyone who
tried to play me!
Now, those who don't want the
same fate should watch their moves!
If this is like the others,
Osman won't stop.
He will kill me and
you will be in line.
Dündar Bey, no one will know that
it was you!
You will be clueless when we enter
the tents.
You are talking about entering
Kayı Tribe, Nikola. What about the tent?
You, Dündar Bey. You will
take us to the tent.
Me?
Then I'll get out of it
like nothing happened?
Dündar Bey, aren't you a Kayı bey?
Where is your courage?
Have you ever betrayed your emperor?
Until you dare to do that, don't you ever
call me a coward. Ever.
All right, Dündar Bey.
You have the right to be afraid.
Then, do you know what will happen?
You'll wait for him to die naturally.
If you have the time and the patience.
I don't have the time or the patience,
Dündar Bey.
If I defeat Osman, Dündar Bey.
Then, I won't need you.
All the tribes that ran away from
Mongols, spread to Anatolia.
Dodurga Tribe is around Bolu,
Çorum and Ankara.
Salur Tribe is around Karaman,
Teke and Candaroğlu lands.
Bayat Tribe is around Karahisar,
Çorum and Bolu.
The bravest of them want to
go further from their borders.
They want jihad,
they want battle, Bamsı Bey.
I know. Ertuğrul Bey
wrote it all...
...on these documents.
We should unite them as once
before they fade out.
We should help them...
...we should give them
lands and tents.
The heathens have lands.
If we kick their lords from there,
we'll locate the tribes.
That's what we will do, Bamsı Bey.
Then, we should invite them.
We should give them the conquered
lands.
They'll join us as they hear it.
And it will be Turkmen tribes everywhere.
-We'll grow even stronger, Bamsı Bey.
-Then, Osman Bey...
...we'll have an army.
-We'll have an army.
And everyone will unite under our banner.
We'll chase the heathens to Constantinople!
Now is the time to go to...
...the tribes of those valiants,
one by one, and invite them.
All right, Osman Be.y
All right.
You will bring Bamsı Bey from
this way.
Germiyan path. There aren't
many guards there.
They'll wait for you there.
Bring Bamsı alone...
...so that he won't create
a problem.
He is scared like a little child that
Osman will take his sword.
He told me to not tell anyone
about his injury.
This will be very easy.
When Bamsı leaves the tents...
...we'll have all the documents.
-What about the caravan?
-Flatyos will bring us the caravan.
Finally, I will give the document to
the Pope.
Three days later, a ship will take
off from the harbor.
And when this is done, you'll kiss
his ring proudly, David.
And for living with these
barbarians for years...
...you will be awarded.
The greatest award is the heaven
of Jesus Christ.
He sighed deeply and said,
“Why does this generation ask for a sign?
Truly I tell you, no sign will
be given to it.”
Then he left them,
got back into the boat...
...and crossed to the other side.
You will tell me what happened
in that castle, Lena!
Bayhoca said that Flatyos
took you to the dungeon.
Don't tell me that it
was a courtesy!
I knew Flatyos from Karacahisar.
I knew that he loved me before
I met you.
Savcı, I hid this from you...
...because I was afraid that
your rage could hurt you.
So, I didn't tell you.
What happened in that castle, Lena?
What happened in that castle?
I begged Flatyos to let
our child go.
So, you begged him?
I've done what a mother in
pain should do, Savcı.
I had hemlock poison with me...
...I was going to save my son
and kill myself.
I wouldn't let them pollute
your honor.
Everyone deserves a second chance, Targun.
If what you say is right,
it will be a good use for me.
If not, then I'll kill you.
By the way, Osman's man, Göktuğ...
...what is he doing with you.
I owe him. He killed my father's killer
with me.
Without Göktuğ, I wouldn't
be leading the Cumans.
So, how will I know that he isn't
Osman's spy.
Just give him a chance. I'll send him
to the caravan with Flatyos.
You will use him like me.
When we get our revenge...
...maybe we'll remember our old
enmities, Nikola.
Don't doubt that, Targun.
So, we'll do this.
Flatyos and Göktuğ will raid the
caravan.
You will go to Söğüt and kill Bala
who has been in the food house lately.
So, we'll see how you and Göktuğ
keep your promises.
-Did you like that?
-Killing Bala?
Is that what you want?
I thought you would like that.
Am I wrong.
Nothing can make me feel that good.
Good. Then everyone to
their job.
Flatyos, keep your eyes
on Göktuğ.
Take his head in his
smallest mistake.
I will behead him if his horse
stumble, Nikola.
Don't get mad later on!
Like you said.
Come on.
The best thing about being an
enemy on open...
...is not being have to hide
like rats.
You shouldn't talk like this to
people who you...
...use their intelligence and plans.
You've done your part.
Now we'll get the documents
and finish Osman.
Meanwhile, you can play games of
war with your soldiers.
Games of war? Do you think it's a game?
I'll make Osman and his loved ones
bleed. You'll steal things...
...and I will kill them.
Then, we can't wait that, Nikola.
Tomorrow, there will be blood.
Osman will bleed. Either
from his head...
...or from his heart.
Now everyone to their jobs.
You are right. Everyone to
their own job.
-May I enter, Osman Bey?
-Come, brother.
Lord of Koyunhisar will go hunting
to meet you in secret tomorrow.
-Thank you, brother.
-Thank you.
-May I enter, my bey?
-Come, Master Davud.
-Salam Alaikum.
-Alaikum Salam.
-You summoned me, my bey.
-Sheikh Edebali is coming here today.
-I want you to greet him.
-We will be honored, my bey.
-Brother, his security is on you.
-Don't worry, brother.
-May I enter, my bey.
-Come, Bala.
-My bey, I have things to say.
-I know.
But...
...my answer is no.
To give birth to a bey's son,
a bey's mother is needed.
Find a good spouse for that woman.
And about the mother of my heir...
...surely, it should be a bey's daughter.
Boran brother, Göktuğ being
banished...
...it's not our place to
question our bey but...
-But what? Don't question it then.
-You are right, brother.
Our Göktuğ should survive and it's
enough. He'll be forgiven one day.
Brother, Nikola's dogs must
be after him.
I know, Gencebay. I know.
Who opened Kulucahisar's gates?
My brother Göktuğ did it.
-He didn't die, did he?
-He didn't.
He won't die. He'll survive.
He won't die but he won't
return either.
-Salam Alaikum.
-Alaikum Salam.
Alps of Kayı, why are you like this?
You are sad about Göktuğ, aren't you?
How did our bey make that decision,
you ask.
But you aren't the bey, you don't know.
A man sleeps by a tree.
The shepherd passing by sees a snake
slipping into the man's mouth.
He hits the man on the head with
his stick. And when the man wakes up...
...he keeps beating him. Until...
...the snake gets out of his mouth.
When the snake leaves, the man realizes
why he was getting beaten.
But, ''You could tell me why you
were beating me first'' he says.
And the shepherd says if I had
told you, you would die in fear.
Alps, when Osman Bey hits
you with his stick...
...don't forget this story.
Don't make a decision until
the snake gets out.
-Thank you, my bey.
I wouldn't think that I Turk
would save my life.
So, you are still a Turk.
When you drink this wine,
I will trust you.
-Where are the spoils?
-Spoils?
Are we thieves?
Why did we kill all these people
if not for the spoils?
Why is it your concern?
Do your job.
It was needed and we've done it.
This won't be done without
blood like Nikola says.
Have ever seen me stepping
back, woman?
It's a big scheme, it's dangerous.
There will be blood. Heads will fall.
If needed, yes.
That's how beys fall...
...that's how the fur changes
hands.
If it's time for the
wolf in sheep disguise...
...to show his teeth...
...may Allah bless our way.
What can I say?
Come at me! Come at me and
taste my sword!
-Surrender!
-Ahmed Alp!
Yiğit Alp!
I yield!
Long live Ahmed Alp!
Long live Yiğit Alp!
-Ahmed, get down. Osman Bey awaits me.
-A little bit more, brother Cerkutay.
You are a man now. I can't carry you.
Get down.
You smartened up.
What does that mean?
You didn't have a brain over
your shoulders before.
I can get Ahmed Alp on my
shoulders to smarten up.
What will you do Aygül the crazy?
Are you so happy, Ahmed Alp?
I forgive you this time
for making Ahmed laugh.
Ahmed Alp, Yiğit Alp
go and play with your brothers.
What happened, Cerkutay?
Are you all right?
You forgave me.
Will Mohammad do the same?
Will you stop stealing too?
There is something else that I need to
steal. Maybe after that.
What's that?
-You are crazy.
-Don't you believe me?
I will gift it to Osman Bey then.
Fine, let's see then.
-All right.
Alps!
-I yield! I yield! I yield!
-Slowly!
I'm running away!
Don't let him run away!
Come on!
Oh, my Allah!
Heal me!
With the name of Allah!
Oh my Allah...
Mashallah, mashallah!
-Salam Alaikum!
-Alaikum Salam! Alaikum Salam!
İdris Bey! İdris Bey!
It's working!
Come on, Bamsı Bey!
Wouldn't I bring it otherwise.
Let's take a look.
Mashallah. Mashallah.
A little bit more and it will be fine.
Yes, yes, Idris bey.
What are you waiting for?
I will, I will but Bamsı Bey.
We ran out of it.
İdris Bey, bring me another one
then.
I will, Bamsı Bey. I will but the
roads aren't safe.
We have to pass the Rum lands.
Nikola's dogs are looking for
Turks to bite.
Don't worry. I'll give you some alps.
I thought you were hiding
your condition, Bamsı Bey.
I don't want it to be heard.
You are right.
Let's go together then, İdris Bey.
If you come with me,
nothing can scare me, Bamsı Bey.
-All right, but don't let anyone understand.
-Come on!
It will be good. It will be good.
Gündüz Bey mentioned a
profitable deal.
I wanted to hear it from you.
So, you aren't afraid of
the price.
There is no price that gold
can't pay.
-What do you want?
-Grasslands.
-I need more grasslands.
-Have your sheep grew in number?
Let's say that it's a preparation
for our holiday.
You are looking for a place for
the new tribes to come.
New tribes, new herds.
You'll grow in power but why
should I say yes?
I will give you 3000 gold coin.
A good price for my animals
to eat your grass.
Let's say that I say yes to you.
Will Nikola let me live after that?
Then, you'll be the lord of İnegöl.
And I will support you.
You want me to betray Nikola.
Do you know its price?
We both know well that there is no
price that gold can't pay.
Well, Osman, let's see what
Nikola will say about that.
You were going to tell it to
Nikola, huh?
Traitor.
Now, you look like a dog
ready to bite his owner.
Come here after 3 days.
I'll tell you my decision.
He is so afraid of Nikola that...
...he plans to sell me out to
make reputation.
He invited me to his trap.
The lord of Koyunhisar
didn't accept. Who is next?
We didn't come here for nothing.
He knew that we invited the tribes.
Then, Nikola knows it.
The lords are aware of
your intentions, my bey.
We aren't done with Yorgo.
My bey, what's on your mind?
Yorgo will give us the head
of the traitor.
We'll sow such discontent among
the lords that...
...they won't have time
for us.
-Abdurrahman Ghazi.
-Yes, my bey.
Go to Yavlak Arslan. Tell him about
this meeting. We don't have time.
Now is the time to fight.
As you order, my bey.
It's an ambush!
Damn it!
Aksu Hatun!
Alps, charge!
An ambush!
Aksu Hatun! Go to the tents at once!
Targun! Charge, alps!
Come on!
Gonca! Gonca!
Go, Bala Hatun!
Come on, come on!
They are running away!
Gonca, come on! Hang on, Gonca!
Come on!
Come on, hurry!
-What's happening, Bamsı Bey?
-It's an ambush.
Bamsı!
Bamsı the mad!
The mad lord!
Do you know what happens to
old deer that walks alone?
I know. I know.
Weasels like you go after it.
Oh, old Bamsı.
Oh...
Old.
Nikola... Nikola...
Nikola...
Look, Nikola. I lived enough.
Thank Allah.
Now, do you know why I'm happy?
When I'm going to Allah,
I won't go empty-handed.
Speaking of hands. They took one
of them.
-I will get the other.
-We'll see. We'll see.
So, old man.
Will you kneel?
Or do we have to make you?
İdris Bey, stand behind me.
Nikola, if you have the courage...
...come and get it.
It's done.
Pope's spy in Kayı Tribe...
...have beaten the old plane, huh?
İdris Bey!
If you want to want me,
come after me!
Run, Bamsı Bey, run.
So that Osman can come.
Catch him!
What did you do?
Don't worry, you won't die.
I know anatomy because
of sculpture.
You will go to the tribe.
You know what to do, don't you?
Get him up.
I live you to the merciful
hands of Jesus, İdris.
Or should I call you David? İdris or
David? David is good.
Damn you!
Gentlemen!
My Allah who created
the sky and the ground!
I greet you!
Give me the strength of Hz.Ali!
Give me the strength of his arms...
...and sharpness of his sword!
You are capable of everything.
Ya Allah!
My Allah, please forgive me!
Bala Hatun...
Osman Bey!
Aksu Hatun!
We were attakced.
Bala Hatun...
-What happened to Bala Hatun?
-At the turnout of Söğüt...
...we were ambushed.
-Who?
Targun...
Targun Hatun.
Alps, take Aksu Hatun to the tribe.
She needs help.
Come on, alps!
Bala! Show yourself!
Go on!
You will be all right, Gonca.
Alps must be on their way.
Be patient.
I'm not sad, Bala. I fought
with you side by side.
-What else can I want?
-Don't speak like this. Someone awaits you.
Hang on a little bit longer.
Boran...
Boran, yes.
Come on, let's go.
Come on!
Gonca...
Come, come!
Come on!
Come on! Come on!
Come, wait here.
It's time to settle up, Bala.
I'm here, Targun.
You'll pay for that poison.
Stop talking and attack me!
Leave her to me, alps!
Attack!
Gonca!
Hang on, Gonca!
Osman and Boran are here!
Damn it!
Help Gonca!
Boran!
Gonca!
You will be all right, Gonca!
You are here...
You are here in time...
Don't tire yourself, Gonca.
You will be all right.
Gonca?
Gonca!
What are you waiting for, brothers?
Hurry! Hurry!
Gonca!
Targun!
-Come on!
-Targun!
This isn't the end, Targun!
-Bala, what is this?
-Targun set us a trap.
Gonca's condition is severe, Osman.
Where are you, Göktuğ?
Where are you?
-Have you figured out what happened?
-While we were waiting for the caravan...
...Targun attacked Bala.
-What are you saying, woman?
She couldn't get into Osman's bed...
...so, she wants to kill Bala.
Aksu is wounded, they brought her
here. She told what happened.
Nikola...
Nikola?
Did you know about this?
What if he brings something
else on us?
May I enter?
Come.
Osman Bey brought Bala Hatun.
-How is she?
-She is fine, thank Allah.
But Gonca Hatun's condition is severe.
I'm going to Osman Bey.
Troubles come without a break.
Lena, what's wrong? Don't you know that...
...this won't end as long as Osman
is leading us?
The troubles comes from Nikola,
not Osman, Hazal Hatun.
Don't you know that?
Lena.
From now, Osman Bey...
...and Bala are my family.
Remember this, Hazal.
-Mother Selcan!
-What's happening?
-Hang on Gonca!
-Gonca? Boil some water!
Mother Selcan, I need your help!
I need your help!
Calm down, son! Is this the first
time you see someone wounded?
It's the first time I see such
a wound, Mother Selcan.
Wait outside now, son.
Come on!
-Is her wound deep?
-It's deep, mother.
-What's this?
-It was my grandmother's
She gave it to my father and
he gave it to me.
-If I die, that's my only heirloom.
-May Allah forbid, Boran Alp!
Why are you talking about death now?
Won't we die someday, Gonca Hatun?
Take these!
Forgive me, Bala Hatun.
Nikola must be behind this.
There is no other explanation.
How will we find that woman?
-Göktuğ is with them, brother?
-You put there a spy?
-Why didn't we hear about the raid?
-That's what I wonder.
It seems that something
happened to Göktuğ.
-May I enter, my bey.
-Come!
İdris Bey! What happened to you?
Who did this?
We were going to a healer with
Bamsı Bey, my bey.
-Bamsı Bey?
-Nikola.
He stopped us with his soldiers.
They wounded me and
chased Bamsı Bey.
Why did you go alone?
Bamsı Bey's hand is injured, my bey.
He didn't want anyone to know it, my bey.
-Boran, prepare the alps. We are leaving.
-Yes, my bey.
What happened, Osman Bey?
Nikola is after Bamsı Bey.
What are you saying, Osman Bey?
Keep your eyes on him, uncle.
I suspect that he might
be Nikola's dog.
I lost Bala.
That was the mission Nikola gave me.
But Osman came in time as always.
I lost many men. It's your turn now,
Göktuğ.
We have to raid Osman's tribe
and get the secret documents.
How will we raid Kayı Tribe after losing
all these men?
Osman won't be at the tribe.
-He'll leave to save Bamsı.
-What happened to Bamsı?
Nikola made a great plan.
We'll enter thanks to him.
Boran. Cerkutay.
My bey, the traces thicken
on this way.
Both ways have traces, my bey.
There is something
wrong with this.
Boran, Gencebey and I will
go this way.
-Brother, you go this way.
-All right, Osman Bey.
-Be cautious. May Allah bless your sword.
-May Allah bless your sword.
Come on! Come on, valiants!
Bamsı!
You tired us so much!
Stop being stubborn!
This is the end of the road!
Come on, Bamsı!
You are too stubborn!
Look, if you surrender, we'll
wait for Osman together.
Don't worry, before
getting the documents...
...I won't kill you or Osman.
The mad lord!
You don't have the power to get
those documents!
You can't even imagine what
my power is enough to get!
Come, come and get me!
Catch this stubborn wolf.
Come...
What will we do now?
Bamsı...
I must be fair.
You are too agile for your age.
And I like good warriors.
He is coming, sir.
Osman is coming.
But you are too stubborn, Bamsı the mad.
Too much.
Come, Osman. Come.
I knew that Targun would bring
bigger troubles, mother.
It won't end before she dies.
My pretty girl, one trouble ends
and the other begins.
Talking about an if is no good
for anyone.
Be cautious.
Be cautious so that you can see
the new troubles.
There is no one left in the tribe, mother.
Anyone but Dündar Bey.
Oh, my girl, oh...
Inshallah the weasels won't try to
take advantage.
If we are left with Dündar...
...then, may Allah protect us.
That idiot, he was about to kill me.
-Salam Alaikum.
-Alaikum Salam, Dündar Bey.
-What's wrong, why is this honor?
-I came to tell you to get well soon.
Mashallah, it was close.
Yeah, it was close.
My Allah protected me.
Was it Allah or Nikola?
What are you saying, Dündar Bey?
Of course, it was Allah.
You must be a good follower.
You survived a trap that Bamsı
couldn't.
Maybe they didn't have anything
to do with me.
They didn't have anything to
do with you, is that so?
Or did they use you to take Bamsı
out of the tribe?
I'm an insignificant potter.
What can I do to Osman Bey?
Dündar Bey.
You are the great Dündar Bey.
If you betray him...
...Osman Bey can't get up again.
Look, the caravan you were waiting
for is here.
I hope it will be profitable, Dündar Bey.
-Salam Alaikum.
-Alaikum Salam. Welcome.
Welcome.
Thank you, Dündar Bey.
Our goods are from Halep...
...Ahlat, Pasinler.
-They are all our old lands.
They are all important for us.
-Where should we leave the goods?
-Back side of the tribe.
Then, you can return to Söğüt.
Mashallah.
Have you taken care of the alps
who stayed here?
I re-positioned them all.
A few guards must be left.
Take Lena and go to Osman Bey's
tent.
It's time. Let's take care of this...
...without making anyone bleed.
Don't worry, my bey.
I just want Osman's corpse to
come to the tribe.
That day will be our holiday.
The tracks go this way.
-These are fake.
-It was a trap.
They wanted to lure us here.
Be careful!
My bey!
Cerkutay.
Are you all right?
Savcı! I brought death for
you and your son.
Now stop hiding and face me
like a man.
Soldiers!
-Son, stay low!
-Don't worry, father.
My beys...
Give me your blessings.
-My blessing is yours.
-Hang on, my valiant!
Don't be sad about me...
...if you had seen what I see now...
...I swear you would
want to go there too.
I bear witness that
there is no god but Allah...
...and I bear witness that Muhammad
is the servant and Messenger of Allah.
-Dumrul!
Flatyos! I will kill you!
Calm down, son!
-Get well soon, Bala Hatun.
-Thank you, Bala Hatun.
Get well soon, Bala Hatun.
Thank Allah that you are all right.
Thank you, Lena Hatun.
Welcome.
So, it was Targun Hatun, huh?
Yes. Let's see who else was
behind that.
Someone will always be.
We need to be careful about the
traitors, Bala Hatun.
You are right.
You've been through difficult days,
Lena Hatun.
While I was sad because my
son would die...
...I was nearly losing my husband.
-May Allah forbid.
-May I enter, my lady.
-Come.
What's wrong, Aksu Hatun.
What are you doing here?
I have things to tell you.
What is it about?
I can't be ungrateful.
Where are you, my bey?
Where are you?
Dündar Bey.
Let's see if you'll be pleased
to see me.
Come on, my bey.
Come on!
Come on! Hurry up!
Come with me.
You were saying something,
Aksu Hatun.
You said that you can't be ungrateful,
why did you say that?
-I said it because--
-Because...
...ungratefulness is the greatest
sin. Isn't that so, daughter?
My lady, I want you to allow me...
...I will return to my mother.
-You should recover first, Aksu Hatun.
-She should go. She should go.
She should recover fully.
The poor girl had been through
a lot.
So, that's how the Kayı Tribe is.
You can't know what will happen.
-Don't worry, I'll send you with alps.
-Thank you, Dündar Bey.
There are many troubles upon us.
We should be cautious.
Surely, surely.
Our best warriors are with Osman Bey.
The heathens are known by
their treachery.
They might attack us from all
sides.
My nephew Gündüz and I took
many measures.
The entrances and exits are
all held...
...by watchers and guards.
From now, only the friends
of the Kayı...
...can enter our tribe.
Bamsı Bey!
Thank Allah!
Osman.
Look, we met again.
-You set a trap, huh?
-Look who is talking.
-You did the same. Many times.
-I entered your place...
...and stabbed you in your heart.
But you are trying to defeat me...
...with many plots and deceptions.
Are you worried about Bamsı?
He fell by the tree saying
''Oh, Osman, oh... Oh...''
He is old. That's normal.
But don't worry. He won't die yet.
I need you alive.
Now, when you have the chance...
...kill me.
Guess who I sent to get your
father's escrows.
Targun Hatun.
When I'm sure that she is done...
...I will kill you slowly.
-What do you want?
-We have gifts for Osman Bey.
Wait here.
-May I enter?
-Come.
My bey, there are gifts for Osman Bey.
Mashallah, it's Osman Bey's caravan.
It's under Osman Bey's protection.
Bring it. Come on.
No one moves!
We met again, Bala!
Targun!
-Göktuğ!
-Traitors...
Ignoble!
What do you want?
Revenge in the cruelest way.
So, Nikola sent you, huh?
And this exile?
You didn't want me to be the
First Alp. So, I became your enemy.
Let's see what will you do now.
Traitors... Traitors don't live long,
Göktuğ. Remember that.
That's not true, Dündar Bey.
If it was, you wouldn't survive this far.
I knew that you were working
with the pope's men.
To be fair, they are very capable, Osman.
Lower this sword.
Let us talk.
Don't take the pleasure of talking to
the greatest enemy I had before killing him.
You snake! You will answer for this!
You won't get out of here alive!
We'll leave thanks
to you.
You wench!
Wench!
Göktuğ, how can you do this
to Osman Bey?
You should've asked this to Osman Bey.
When he insulted me and kicked me,
you should've asked how could he do that.
You couldn't do a single job.
You let Flatyos run away.
Now are you blaming
Osman Bey for this?
I was just in power. I was with
Osman Bey when he ran away.
Now I'm in his tent.
I came for revenge.
Enough, Göktuğ.
Now it's my turn.
Let's enter Osman Bey's private room.
-Don't try it, don't, Targun!
-Stop me if you can.
Don't! No! No!
Targun, no! Don't! No!
-Get out of there, Targun!
-Hurry, search everywhere.
No!
Osman Bey...
If you had chosen me, you would
be the greatest of the beys.
Now you'll lose everything you have.
Traitors... Traitors...
No! No...
So, you will build a state, Osman Bey?
Let's see how you'll build it now.
Come on, take these.
Come on.
No... No...
-Come on, we are leaving.
-Targun.
Osman took his lesson.
We shouldn't give these to Nikola.
We don't want him to get stronger.
No.
We'll honor the deal.
-We should press him further.
-I said no!
-Bala Hatun...
-Traitor!
Bala Hatun!
No...
Bala Hatun. Be careful.
Treachery is everywhere.
No... No...
Göktuğ!
With the name of Allah!
Thank Allah for returning to lands of
Ertuğrul Ghazi's son Osman Bey.
-What's wrong, Kumral Abdal?
-My Sheikh. I came to you...
...to learn of secrets.
I heard that...
...Osman Bey's tribe will be raided.
Help!
You did everything you could.
You did everything you could
against a smarter, stronger enemy.
But everything was for nothing.
Your tribe is raided, your father's
escrows, the documents are taken.
And probably there is a slaughter
going on in your tribe.
Ignoble dog!
But I'm still breathing!
Osman! Osman!
-Bamsı Bey!
-Bamsı Bey has awaken!
Osman!
We were just about to kill Osman.
Of course, unless you kneel and beg.
Osman, what does this dog speaks of?
You will kneel and beg, for your
beloved ones.
Then, you'll kiss my boots.
Osman, today is the day we die.
Bamsı Bey, firstly...
...let us send them to hell.
So, you want to die?
Osman Bey, as you say...
...victory belongs to those who
sharpen their weapon with their faith.
-Victory?
-Victory!
It belongs to those who stand together!
-To death!
-To victory!
Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com